

CONTACT

Phone

+91-8144573354

Email

satyaprofessional99@gmail.com

Address

Balasore, Odisha, India

SOCIALS



/Satyana17786386



/satyadalei



https://satyadalei.github.io/portfolio/



/satyadalei

LANGUAGES

- English
- Odia
- Hindi

SATYANARAYAN **DALEI**

WFB DFVFI OPFR

(Fullstack Developer)

About Me

I am a full-stack developer. I have over one year of experience working in this field. Working in cooperative teams inspires me greatly and lets my skills thrive. The backend side is my core field of expertise. I like music and sometimes travelling too.

EDUCATIONS

Master In Computer Application (MCA)

Indira Gandhi Institute of Technology 2022 - Ongoing

Bachelor of Physics

North Orissa University 2018-21 CGPA 7.97

CERTIFICATES

Web Development BootCamp | 2021

Dr. Angella Yu || Udemy Course

SKILLS

FrontEnd

Backend

Frameworks

HTML

• Express.Js

Bootstrap 5

- CSS
- MongoDB
- Javascript
- React

All projects are on my Github Page

WORK EXPERIENCE



Junior Web Developer & Designer

2021-22 June - Ms Info Systems.



Designer and Photo Editor

2020-21 - Rainbow Studio, Baripada